<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on A Demo for Hugo</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on A Demo for Hugo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.125.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:08:46 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Second</title>
      <link>/posts/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:08:46 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/second/</guid>
      <description>Amateur Radio in 2024 As of 2024, amateur radio continues to thrive as a dynamic and evolving hobby worldwide, including in the UK. Despite the advancements in digital communication technologies, the allure of amateur radio persists, offering a unique blend of traditional radio communication and modern innovation.
In the UK, amateur radio enthusiasts remain active in exploring new frontiers of communication, experimenting with cutting-edge technologies such as software-defined radios (SDRs), digital modes, and satellite communication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First</title>
      <link>/posts/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:08:30 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/first/</guid>
      <description>Amateur Radio in the UK Amateur radio, also known as ham radio, holds a longstanding tradition in the United Kingdom, dating back over a century. Enthusiasts of all ages and backgrounds come together in this vibrant community, driven by a shared passion for communication, exploration, and service.
The UK amateur radio scene is regulated by Ofcom, ensuring that operators adhere to licensing requirements and frequency allocations. This regulatory framework fosters a diverse ecosystem where individuals can experiment with radio technology, engage in emergency communications, and participate in contests and events.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
